{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622698","name":"Torta Express","address":"23601 Cedar Ridge Dr","zipcode":"48174","owner":"Jessica Villagomex","licenseNumber":"229274","licenseType":"Special Transitory Food Unit","establishmentType":"LHD - Mobile Food Establishmen","establishmentStatus":"Seasonal","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"395","coords":"","geojson":{"id":"51622698","type":"Feature","geometry":null,"properties":{"name":"Torta Express","owner":"Jessica Villagomex","address":"23601 Cedar Ridge Dr","zipcode":"48174","license_type":"Special Transitory Food Unit","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"229274","establishmentid":"51622698","establishment_type":"LHD - Mobile Food Establishmen","establishment_status":"Seasonal","review_frequency_days":"395","most_recent_license_date":"4/24/2019"}},"nearbyList":[],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45905","inspectionDate":"2019-04-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\r\n\r\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Glove usage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Replace."},{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"HOT WATER","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-401.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT, a cabinet used for the storage of FOOD, or a cabinet that is used to store cleaned and SANITIZED EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES may not be located in an unsuitable areas or where exposed to possible contamination.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored","subProblem":"Under other source of contamination","location":"CEILING","subLocation":"Water","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-04-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-402.12","violationDescription":"If used, a grease trap shall be located to be easily accessible for cleaning.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Grease trap","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HOOD","subLocation":"Grease collection device","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-04-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44694","inspectionDate":"2018-10-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-10-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-10-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-10-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"42208","inspectionDate":"2018-05-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Final/Ap","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622698"}}